<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Assignments on HIS393: Digital History</title>
    <link>https://digitalhistory.github.io/wdw235/assignment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Assignments on HIS393: Digital History</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 15:58:25 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://digitalhistory.github.io/wdw235/assignment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Project: Book Exhibit</title>
      <link>https://digitalhistory.github.io/wdw235/assignment/book-project-assignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 15:58:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalhistory.github.io/wdw235/assignment/book-project-assignment/</guid>
      <description>Overview In this assignment, you get to tell the story of a banned book you have seen in person, either from the Thomas Fisher Rare Book Library or from our list.
You will create a website that features a digital collection and exhibit about that book, using the free, open-source content management platform Omeka. Like a good museum curator, you will bring together a gallery of exciting pictures, and you will guide your visitors through that gallery through a well-researched, interesting narrative about your book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Project: Proposal</title>
      <link>https://digitalhistory.github.io/wdw235/assignment/book-project-proposal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 15:55:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalhistory.github.io/wdw235/assignment/book-project-proposal/</guid>
      <description>Please use this page to hand in your project proposals. For a description of the assignment, see the main project assignment page.
Rubric Description of book and ban :
Feasibility of Project :
Style &amp;amp; Grammar :
Grade :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Project: Consultation</title>
      <link>https://digitalhistory.github.io/wdw235/assignment/consultation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 15:54:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalhistory.github.io/wdw235/assignment/consultation/</guid>
      <description>Rubric  Grade:  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflection 02: The Ruin</title>
      <link>https://digitalhistory.github.io/wdw235/assignment/reflection-2-the-ruin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 19:21:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalhistory.github.io/wdw235/assignment/reflection-2-the-ruin/</guid>
      <description>Before completing this assignment, read the recently revised, HTML version of the handout “The Ruin: Digital Literary Studies” and carry out the exercises it asks you to do.
  What is The Ruin? Briefly describe the poem and its themes. State what passage you are focusing on and analyze its poetic characteristics, as discussed in class. Be specific; cite poem by line numbers. Cite Echard&#39;s online translation correctly using the citation format of your choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflection 02: Handout and Preliminary Exercises</title>
      <link>https://digitalhistory.github.io/wdw235/assignment/reflection-2-handout/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 09:55:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalhistory.github.io/wdw235/assignment/reflection-2-handout/</guid>
      <description>In this assignment, you will encode parts of a thousand-year-old poem using a markup language, display the marked-up text in a web browser using a computational translator, and discuss this exercise using the idea of deformance as a guide. This handout should contain everything you need to complete the assignment, but please use the discussion forum to ask any technical (or other!) questions.
The Poem: “The Ruin” (from the tenth century Exeter Book), translated by Sian Echard, silently emended &amp;ldquo;The Ruin&amp;rdquo; was likely written in the 8th or 9th century, and recorded in the Exeter Book in the 10th century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflection 01: DH Project Profile</title>
      <link>https://digitalhistory.github.io/wdw235/assignment/reflection-1-project-profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 12:14:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalhistory.github.io/wdw235/assignment/reflection-1-project-profile/</guid>
      <description>Your first assignment is to profile a Digital Humanities project, analyzing its research aims, its form and content, its interface, technologies, and intended audience. You will learn how to navigate Digital Humanities projects, how to identify and evaluate different aspects of such projects, and how to analyze the kinds of knowledge and digital artifacts generated by DH projects. Write-up: 500 words plus screenshots.
You may select any project you like from the syllabus or from one of the pages below:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://digitalhistory.github.io/wdw235/assignment/02-maps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalhistory.github.io/wdw235/assignment/02-maps/</guid>
      <description>02: Maps .underline { text-decoration: underline; }   /* Position computations of klipse get confused by reveal.js&#39;s scaling. Hence, scaling should be disabled with this code. Fix height of code area with scrollbar (use overflow instead of overflow-y to restore CodeMirror setting afterwards): */ .reveal section pre { max-height: 70vh; height: auto; overflow: auto; } /* Reset some reveal.js and oer-reveal settings: */ .reveal section pre .CodeMirror pre { font-size: 2em; box-shadow: none; width: auto; padding: 0.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>